{
    "name": ".\\Italian\\Chapter6.json",
    "vocab": [
        {
            "alternates": [
                "ospedale"
            ],
            "answer": "(un) ospedale",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518459241.3967602,
            "question": "Given the definition \"hospital\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "There is a church on Mazzini street"
            ],
            "answer": "There is a church on Mazzini Street.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518459157.805485,
            "question": "Given the definition \"C'e' una chiesa in via Mazzini.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "buon viaggio",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518459245.3583317,
            "question": "Given the definition \"have a good trip\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "vicine",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518459168.034296,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"near (plural feminine)\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "through",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1518459259.036598,
            "question": "Given the definition \"per\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "C'e un cinema in viale Roma",
                "C'e un cinema in viale ROma"
            ],
            "answer": "C'e' un cinema in viale Roma.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1518459256.7818646,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Where is a movie theater on Roma Avenue?\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "ospedale, lontano",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518459230.6051435,
            "question": "The hospital is far. L'___ e' ____.",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "left"
            ],
            "answer": "on the left, to the left",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518459237.0299053,
            "question": "Given the definition \"(a) sinistra\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "ristorante"
            ],
            "answer": "(un) ristorante",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518459268.040734,
            "question": "Given the definition \"restaurant\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "vicina",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518459271.4000602,
            "question": "La famracia e' (near).",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "sinistra"
            ],
            "answer": "(a) sinistra",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518459286.1165686,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"on the left, to the left\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "school",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518459263.8805628,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"(una) scuola\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "kind",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1518459309.0762386,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"gentile/gentili\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "per",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518459261.0566032,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"through\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "vicino",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1518459305.3889024,
            "question": "Le scuole sono qui (near).",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "vicino",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1518459302.9575176,
            "question": "La famracia e' (near) all stazione.",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "vicini",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1518459349.1719465,
            "question": "Gli ospedali sono (near).",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "second",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518459317.711656,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"secondo/seconda/secondi/seconde\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "vicino"
            ],
            "answer": "vicino / vicina / vicini / vicine",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518459312.3916411,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"near\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "cinema"
            ],
            "answer": "(un) cinema",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518459337.2918339,
            "question": "Given the definition \"movie theater\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "gentili",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518459341.7432406,
            "question": "La madre e' gentile. Le madri sono ___",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "banca"
            ],
            "answer": "(una) banca",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518459322.7277937,
            "question": "Given the definition \"bank\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "nearby"
            ],
            "answer": "near (plural feminine)",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518459333.4675102,
            "question": "Given the definition \"vicine\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "excellent",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518459345.955541,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"eccelente/eccelenti\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "excuse me"
            ],
            "answer": "excuse me (informal)",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1518459404.7546916,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"scusa\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "excuse me"
            ],
            "answer": "excuse me (formal)",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518459402.1307456,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"scusi\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "happy birthday",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518459390.4949293,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"buon compleanno\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "vicino",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1518459409.6913002,
            "question": "I supermercati sono (near) alla stazione.",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "near"
            ],
            "answer": "near (singular feminine)",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518459354.4520288,
            "question": "Given the definition \"vicina\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "gentili"
            ],
            "answer": "gentile/gentili",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518459382.032418,
            "question": "Given the definition \"kind\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "The museum is next to the station"
            ],
            "answer": "The museum is next to the station.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518459374.3671744,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Il museo e' vicino alla stazione.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "vicino",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518459385.9833593,
            "question": "La stazione e' (near) all abanca.",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Il teatro e' vicino alla Chiesa"
            ],
            "answer": "Il teatro e' vicino alla chiesa.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1518459626.844732,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"The theater is next to the church.\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "fino a",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1518459600.7845037,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"up to\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "C'e un cinema in viale Roma"
            ],
            "answer": "C'e' un cinema in viale Roma.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1518459585.4533434,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"There is a movie theater on Roma Avenue.\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "C'e una farmacia in piazza Dante"
            ],
            "answer": "C'e' una farmacia in piazza Dante.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1518459611.273219,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"There is a pharmacy in Dante Square.\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Have a good walk!",
                "enjoy your walk"
            ],
            "answer": "Enjoy your walk!",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1518459633.0453875,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Buona passeggiata!\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "vicino",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518459441.126659,
            "question": "La banca e' qui (near).",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "C'e una banca qui vicino?"
            ],
            "answer": "C'e' una banca qui vicino?",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1518459595.672859,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Is there a bank nearby?\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "lontano"
            ],
            "answer": "lontano / lontana / lontani / lontane",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518459531.077579,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"far\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "sempre diritto",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1518459686.4849772,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"straight ahead\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "vicini",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518459649.5680635,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"near (plural masculine)\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "scuola"
            ],
            "answer": "(una) scuola",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518459666.2038097,
            "question": "Given the definition \"school\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "primo"
            ],
            "answer": "primo/prima/primi/prime",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518459676.259764,
            "question": "Given the definition \"first\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "secondo"
            ],
            "answer": "secondo/seconda/secondi/seconde",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518459662.824407,
            "question": "Given the definition \"second\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "vicino",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518459680.9154997,
            "question": "Gli ospedali sono (near) alla scuola.",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "There is a movie theater on Roma avenue"
            ],
            "answer": "Where is a movie theater on Roma Avenue?",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518459644.0643182,
            "question": "Given the definition \"C'e' un cinema in viale Roma.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "intersection",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518459672.707858,
            "question": "Given the definition \"incrocio\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "stazione, vicino, scuola",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1518459766.4307795,
            "question": "The train station is next to the school. La ___ e' ___ alla ___.",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "supermarket"
            ],
            "answer": "a supermarket",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518459742.5225697,
            "question": "Given the definition \"un supermercato\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "destra"
            ],
            "answer": "(a) destra",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518459699.8079028,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"on the right, to the right\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "teatro, piazza",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518459752.446518,
            "question": "And there's a theater in Dante Square. E c'e' un ___ in ___ Dante.",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "vicina",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518459756.255169,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"near (singular feminine)\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Il museo e' vicino alla stazione"
            ],
            "answer": "Il museo e' vicino alla stazione.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518459737.9634438,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"The museum is next to the station.\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "vicine",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518459704.7527525,
            "question": "La scuola e' vicina. Le scuole sono ___",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "vicino",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518459760.3667266,
            "question": "La chiesa e' qui (near).",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "far",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518459830.097542,
            "question": "Given the definition \"lontano / lontana / lontani / lontane\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "banca, ufficio",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518459822.2699165,
            "question": "The bank and the post office are downtown. La ___ e l'___ postale sono in centro.",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "again",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1518459874.124842,
            "question": "Given the definition \"ancora\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "ancora",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1518459828.213907,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"again\"?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "un supermercato",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1518459857.4215987,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"a supermarket\"?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "buona passeggiata"
            ],
            "answer": "Buona passeggiata!",
            "failed": 6,
            "lastAsked": 1518459877.885557,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Enjoy your walk!\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "buon compleanno",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1518459834.1065266,
            "question": "Given the definition \"happy birthday\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "C'e una banca qui vicino."
            ],
            "answer": "C'e' una banca qui vicino.",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1518459794.9618158,
            "question": "Given the definition \"There is a bank nearby.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "buon anniversario",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1518460044.1711013,
            "question": "Given the definition \"happy anniversary\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "C'e una chiesa in via Mazzini"
            ],
            "answer": "C'e' una chiesa in via Mazzini.",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1518459969.2164319,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"There is a church on Mazzini Street.\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "C'e, cinema"
            ],
            "answer": "C'e', cinema",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1518460036.7876441,
            "question": "There's a movie theater on Mazzini street. ___ un ___ in via Mazzini.",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "la scuola e' qui vicino"
            ],
            "answer": "La scuola e' qui vicino.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1518459920.8134167,
            "question": "Given the definition \"The school is nearby.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "up to",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1518460039.1394043,
            "question": "Given the definition \"fino a\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Dov'e la stazione?"
            ],
            "answer": "Dov'e' la stazione?",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1518459957.6408343,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Where is the train station?\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "ufficio postale"
            ],
            "answer": "un officio postale",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1518459906.6645725,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"a post office\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "teatro"
            ],
            "answer": "(un) teatro",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1518459900.0328074,
            "question": "Given the definition \"theater\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "first",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1518460063.9112456,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"primo/prima/primi/prime\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "right"
            ],
            "answer": "on the right, to the right",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1518460075.8312674,
            "question": "Given the definition \"(a) destra\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "incrocio",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1518460120.1665015,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"intersection\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "happy holidays",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1518460106.8785977,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"buone feste\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "buone feste",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1518460109.838706,
            "question": "Given the definition \"happy holidays\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "buona cena"
            ],
            "answer": "Buona cena!",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1518460061.8387694,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Enjoy your dinner!\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "bon voyage"
            ],
            "answer": "have a good trip",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1518460096.3714166,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"buon viaggio\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "farmacia, vicina",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1518460116.0706792,
            "question": "The pharmacy, on the other hand, is near. La ___, inceve, e' ___.",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "scusi",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1518460148.153995,
            "question": "Given the definition \"excuse me (formal)\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Il ristorante e' vicino alla scuola"
            ],
            "answer": "Il ristorante e' vicino alla scuola.",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1518460209.9412158,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"The restaurant is next to the school.\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "The restaurant is next to the school"
            ],
            "answer": "The restaurant is next to the school.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1518460156.514087,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Il ristorante e' vicino alla scuola.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "There is a movie theater on Roma street"
            ],
            "answer": "There is a movie theater on Roma Avenue.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1518460168.5827339,
            "question": "Given the definition \"C'e' un cinema in viale Roma.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "post office"
            ],
            "answer": "a post office",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1518460143.6747084,
            "question": "Given the definition \"un officio postale\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "lontane",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1518460214.709285,
            "question": "La banca e' lontana. Le banche sono ___",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "The pharmacy is on Dante square"
            ],
            "answer": "There is a pharmacy in Dante Square.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1518460181.1100311,
            "question": "Given the definition \"C'e' una farmacia in piazza Dante.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "interessanti",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1518460198.6422827,
            "question": "Il museo e' interessante. I musei sono ___",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "farmacia"
            ],
            "answer": "(una) farmacia",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1518460250.0895572,
            "question": "Given the definition \"pharmacy\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "scusa",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1518460264.1289074,
            "question": "Given the definition \"excuse me (informal)\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "citta'",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1518460276.5573306,
            "question": "This is my hometown. Questa e' la mia ___ natale.",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "buon riposo",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1518460279.3572347,
            "question": "Given the definition \"have a good rest\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "poi",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1518460285.3806393,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"then\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "buona fortuna",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1518460259.4246795,
            "question": "Given the definition \"good luck\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "vicino",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1518460221.3654487,
            "question": "Le scuole sono (near) alla banca.",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "buon Natale",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1518460282.8049476,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Merry Christmas\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "straight ahead",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1518460338.987286,
            "question": "Given the definition \"sempre diritto\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "vicino",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1518460342.9156735,
            "question": "La farmacia e' qui (near).",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "The school is near"
            ],
            "answer": "The school is near.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518460307.0322225,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"La scuola e' vicina.\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "a pharmacy"
            ],
            "answer": "pharmacy",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518460313.7282043,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"(una) farmacia\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "close"
            ],
            "answer": "near (plural masculine)",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518460334.2040443,
            "question": "Given the definition \"vicini\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "vicine",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518460298.1530123,
            "question": "Le scuole sono (near).",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "l'ospedale",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518460290.0288322,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"the hospital\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "vicina",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518460328.2762198,
            "question": "La banca e' (near).",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "vicino",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518460414.239341,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"near (singular masculine)\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "hospital",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518460417.5434997,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"(un) ospedale\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "La scuola e' vicina"
            ],
            "answer": "La scuola e' vicina.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1518460432.3716514,
            "question": "Given the definition \"The school is near.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "lontani",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1518460436.218949,
            "question": "L'ospedale e' lontano. Gli ospedali sono ___",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "vicina",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518460353.4402037,
            "question": "La banca e' (near).",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "Is there a bank nearby?",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518460368.423822,
            "question": "Given the definition \"C'e' una banca qui vicino?\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "semaforo",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518460346.7394323,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"traffic light\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "museum",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518460349.852282,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"(un) museo\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "bank",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518460485.938495,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"(una) banca\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "vicino",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518460482.5302389,
            "question": "L'ufficio postale e' (near).",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "vicini",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518460447.3550956,
            "question": "Il semaforo e' vicino. I semafori sono ____",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "The school is close"
            ],
            "answer": "The school is nearby.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518460479.5063872,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"La scuola e' qui vicino.\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "in centro",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518460472.8945706,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"downtown\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "la scuola e' vicino alla Chiesa",
                "la scuola e' vicino alla chiesa"
            ],
            "answer": "La scuola e' vicino alla chiesa.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518460466.4945636,
            "question": "Given the definition \"The school is next to the church.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "Where is the station?"
            ],
            "answer": "Where is the train station?",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518460441.9139953,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Dov'e' la stazione?\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "chiesa"
            ],
            "answer": "(una) chiesa",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518460453.7587104,
            "question": "Given the definition \"church\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "close"
            ],
            "answer": "near (singular masculine)",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518460506.6703646,
            "question": "Given the definition \"vicino\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "There is a bank nearby"
            ],
            "answer": "There is a bank nearby.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1518460548.2534952,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"C'e' una banca qui vicino.\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "stazione"
            ],
            "answer": "(una) stazione",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518460495.3660688,
            "question": "Given the definition \"train station\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "vicino",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518460522.9858246,
            "question": "Il ristorante e' (near) alla farmacia.",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "The school"
            ],
            "answer": "the school",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518460500.6463645,
            "question": "Given the definition \"la scuola\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "vicina",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518460503.1904354,
            "question": "La scuola e' (near).",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "have a good dinner"
            ],
            "answer": "Enjoy your dinner!",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518460512.605964,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Buona cena!\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "eccelenti",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518460517.8856091,
            "question": "La scuola e' eccelente. Le scuole sono ___",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "have a good rest",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518460567.797357,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"buon riposo\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "vicino",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518460559.2852101,
            "question": "La banca e' (near) alla chiesa.",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "good luck",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518460581.8286245,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"buona fortuna\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "church",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518460552.485638,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"(una) chiesa\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "simpatici",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518460555.8295357,
            "question": "Il padre e' simpatico. I padri sono ___",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "downtown",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518460562.789423,
            "question": "Given the definition \"in centro\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "traffic light",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1518460589.736984,
            "question": "Given the definition \"semaforo\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "and then"
            ],
            "answer": "then",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518460586.0975397,
            "question": "Given the definition \"poi\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "restaurant",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518460621.685295,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"(un) ristorante\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "The school is next to the church"
            ],
            "answer": "The school is next to the church.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518460597.6889577,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"La scuola e' vicino alla chiesa.\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "la scuola",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518460600.1610048,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"the school\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "movie theater",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518460603.9084587,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"(un) cinema\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "hospital"
            ],
            "answer": "the hospital",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518460611.3566556,
            "question": "Given the definition \"l'ospedale\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "eccelenti"
            ],
            "answer": "eccelelenti",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518460629.008792,
            "question": "Il ristorante e' eccelente. I ristoranti sono ___",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "post office",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518460618.916528,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"(un) officio postale\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "train station",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518460607.156656,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"(una) stazione\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "merry christmas"
            ],
            "answer": "Merry Christmas",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518460676.5120983,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"buon Natale\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "chiesa, centro",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518460669.9605043,
            "question": "The church is downtown, too. Anche la ___ e' in ___.",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "eccelente"
            ],
            "answer": "eccelente/eccelenti",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1518460693.1668718,
            "question": "Given the definition \"excellent\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "museo"
            ],
            "answer": "(un) museo",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518460658.3094966,
            "question": "Given the definition \"museum\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "supermarket",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518460654.7484736,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"(un) supermercato\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "vicine",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1518460689.8163767,
            "question": "Le scuole sono (near).",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "close"
            ],
            "answer": "near",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518460661.3447347,
            "question": "Given the definition \"vicino / vicina / vicini / vicine\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "supermercato"
            ],
            "answer": "(un) supermercato",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518460683.2877996,
            "question": "Given the definition \"supermarket\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "happy anniversary",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518460705.2676566,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"buon anniversario\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "vicini",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518460696.4156134,
            "question": "L'ufficio postale e' vicino. Gli uffici postali sono ___.",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "ufficio postale"
            ],
            "answer": "(un) officio postale",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518460710.1838033,
            "question": "Given the definition \"post office\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "theater",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518460700.996747,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"(un) teatro\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "The theater is next to the church"
            ],
            "answer": "The theater is next to the church.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1518460718.2874398,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Il teatro e' vicino alla chiesa.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        }
    ]
}